Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resync by GoldenBeard
Budapest.
The next stop's Budapest.
Budapest is the next stop.
Budapest.
Tickets, ladies.
Oop, here you go.
- Here's mine.
- And mine.
- Mine, too!
- Here you go!
Thank you, young man.
Man, I hate wearing disguises.
These heels are killing me.
Okay, take it down a notch.
We don't want to alarm
the humans.
Psst. Drac.
I'm about to und freak out!
You're a nice kitty.
I'm und kitty-cat.
Meow. Meow!
Oh, no,
not this clown again.
Good evening, travelers.
I am Professor
Abraham Van Helsing.
Yes. One of the Van Helsings.
For centuries, my family
has protected humanity
from the evils of monsters.
So you can believe me
when I tell you,
there are monsters
hiding amongst you!
But fear not,
for I am a professional,
and I know how to flush out
these beasts
and bring them into the light!
Fire bad!
Whoa!
Sorry, guys.
Finally! First I kill Dracula,
and then
the rest of the monsters!
Why do you keep doing this?
Your dad, your grandfather,
your great-great-granny...
I defeated them all.
When will you Van Helsings ever
learn to let go of the hate?
Never! Because you,
monster, are a...
Eh, squeak, squeak.
What? A mouse?
Ahhh!
You can't run from me,
Prince of Darkness!
I will hunt you
for all eternity!
I swear I will never rest until
I destroy you...
And...
Every...
Other...
Monster... Ow!
If it's the last thing...
I...
Ever...
Do!
Boy, that guy is annoying.
Maybe one day
there will be a place
where monsters can go
to get away from it all,
take a vacation.
Who knows,
maybe even get married.
Wouldn't that be something?
Hmm?
It's okay.
Oh, when is
this thing starting?
Aw, you made them cry,
Wayne.
All except this little one.
Coochie-coochie...
That's Sunny.
She doesn't cry.
She bites.
This is a very special moment, Carl.
Any second, your beautiful bride is
going to walk right down the aisle.
Oh, no, Drac,
she's not coming.
Oh, don't worry.
Mavis is with her. I'm sure
everything is under control.
Mavey, is everything
under control?
Um, yep, just a slight case
of pre-wedding jitters.
Ahhh!
Yep, everything is
fine here.
Please try to relax, Lucy.
I've taken care
of everything.
The wedding
is going to be perfect.
It's not that.
Just, how do I know
I'm doing the right thing?
I know just how you feel.
The day I married Johnny was
the best day of my life,
but I was so nervous.
Not as nervous
as I was.
And you should have seen my dad.
He was a mess.
I wouldn't get out
of my coffin that night.
But he knew
it was meant to be.
It doesn't matter
where you come from
or how different
you are.
A Zing only happens
once in your life,
and you have to
cherish it.
Aw.
You're right! Thank you!
Okay.
All right. Okay.
Oh. Uh... Okay.
I do.
Do you hear that?
Yes. I thought we
locked him in his room.
We did!
Whoa! Whoa!
Hi, Mom. Hi, Papa.
- Dennis!
Tinkles was crying,
so we let him out.
Ahhh!
Tinkles, sit!
Ah. Whose idea was it
to let Dennis have a puppy?
Um... Yours?
Right.
Poor Tinkles.
Dennis...
Look, honey,
I know you love Tinkles,
but we're not allowed
to bring our dogs...
Uh... I mean, our pets everywhere.
Okay?
Okay.
DJ Jazzy Johnny in the house.
It's time to welcome the happy
couple, Mr. and Mrs. Prickles!
Aw!
The bride and groom
invite everyone
to join them
on the dance floor.
Care to dance?
Is that her?
Ooh! Watch out now.
She got stitches
in all the right places.
Okay, there's no way that
is related to you, Frank.
No, she's
my right arm's cousin.
Ay! Oh!
- Oh!
- Ah! I see it now.
Frank wanted me to meet you.
We're arm cousins,
twice removed.
Of course.
I'd recognize that bicep
anywhere.
He thought, since we're both
single, we might hit it off,
maybe go on a date?
"Date"? Oh!
Well, eh,
it's just that, eh...
Whoa!
The DJ booth
is a sacred space!
I love this song!
Don't you?
Dracula?
Oh, where'd he go?
What's the matter, Drac,
you didn't like her?
No offense, but you
can't be too picky.
You haven't had a date
in 100 years.
Look, guys, I appreciate your
concern, but it's not up to me.
You only Zing once,
and I did.
Times have changed, buddy.
You can even find someone to
Zing with on your phone now.
What? Really?
Oh. Oh, no, no, no.
I'm far too busy.
I have Mavis and Dennis and the
hotel, and bleh, bleh-bleh.
Um, did you guys
hear that?
He actually said,
"Bleh, bleh-bleh."
I don't say,
"Bleh, bleh-bleh"!
Eh, uh,
I'm looking for a Zing.
Okay. Changing phone ring.
No, no.
I'm looking for a date.
No, no, no.
I want to meet someone.
Are you kidding me right now?
Don't you get it?
I want to go on a date!
I'm lonely.
You want baloney.
What? Look at
that hair. Come on.
Ah. Too many eyes.
Too few eyes.
Not into tentacles.
"Match found"?
No, no, no!
First things first.
Whoa!
I'm not into games.
You'd better have a job,
and my cats have to like you.
Oh, no.
Oh, whoa, no.
Dad?
Oh! Mavis! Oh.
Uh, what are you doing here?
I was just checking on the honeymoon
suite, and I heard something.
Oh, I'm sorry,
my little bedbug.
I was just cleaning
the attic.
It's so dirty, ah, yes...
- Who is that?
- Are you on the phone?
What, this? I was just
trying to find a maid
- to help me with the mess.
- A maid?
Who do you think...
Thank you,
I'll check your references
and get back to you. Goodbye!
Dad.
Stop trying to
hide it from me.
Hide? Who?
I mean, what? Me?
Yes.
And I know what it is.
Uh... Really?
You're stressed out
from working too hard.
Oh!
Okay, yes.
You got me.
It's a big hotel,
you know?
Can't get to everything.
But what about you?
You're pretty busy yourself.
I know. It seems like now that
we're working together more,
we're seeing
each other less.
Ah. Yeah.
You're absolutely right.
I am working too much,
you're working too much.
We should really take a break,
starting right now.
Night-night.
I'm still here!
Aw.
Oh! Hey, honey.
You ready for
date night?
Aw.
That's okay, sweetheart.
You rest.
You know, Dad's right.
We need a break.
We need to all be together
again, like a family.
Like we used to.
Are you
overworked and stressed out?
Do you need some family time?
Are you a monster?
Then you need a vacation,
a monster vacation.
Welcome aboard
Gremlin Air.
Ah!
Ladies and gentlemen,
please direct your attention
to the front of the cabin.
For your safety, please
unbuckle your seat belts.
Ooh.
In the likely event we experience
a sudden drop in cabin pressure,
oxygen will be provided.
Can I stow that
for you, sir?
All right. Thanks.
Beverages. Snacks. Beverages.
Beverages. Snacks.
Beverages.
Ahhh!
- Coffee?
- That would be lovely.
Mavis, please,
you're torturing me.
You know I hate surprises.
This is
a fun surprise.
There are no fun surprises.
Just tell me
where we're going.
Why are we on a plane?
We can fly, you know.
Back in my day,
people took trains.
Now, that's classy.
Sure, Dad. Forty hours
in a closet-sized room
with you and Uncle Bernie
and his smelly cigars,
arguing who was
more attractive,
Cleopatra or Nefertiti.
Nefertiti.
Okay, Dad, thank you.
Mavis, this is
such an amazing surprise!
I can't wait to spend time
with the people I love most.
But I beg of you,
tell me where we're going!
Nope. I've taken care of everything,
so you don't need to worry.
You've been
so stressed out lately.
It's time for you to relax.
Now, isn't that better?
Oh, yes.
So relaxed.
I'm gonna go check
on you-know-who.
I'll be right back.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Hey, did you see that?
Dennis went to the bathroom!
Uh... Okay.
Psst. Hey, where are you?
There you are, Tinkles.
Don't worry, we'd never
leave you home alone.
Okay, folks,
you're free to move
about the cabin, as we have
started our descent.
So, any big plans
for the weekend there, Bill?
Oh, you know,
the usual.
Got to take the kids
to soccer.
Snacks. Beverages.
Snacks. Beverages. Snacks.
Ladies and gentlemen, we've
arrived at our destination,
the Bermuda Triangle.
Ooh!
Welcome to
the Bermuda Triangle,
where you'll embark on a
monster cruise of a lifetime.
A cruise?
Surprise!
Oh, no, you... No.
But it's just like a hotel
on the water.
I just figured
you need a vacation
from running
everyone else's vacation.
You've barely been
out of the hotel since...
Well, since Mom died.
But this is a chance
to make new memories,
with all of us.
With Dennis.
- Boat!
Who made you
such an amazing daughter?
You.
That's right!
What a father I am.
Come on, Denisovich,
let's get cruising!
Yay!
Wow!
Okay. Smile.
Thank you.
Ow!
"No pets allowed"?
Uh-oh.
Perfect.
Welcome aboard.
How are you doing?
- Dennis, come on.
- Nice to see you.
Oh, lovely shirt. Yes.
Oh, hello.
Welcome aboard.
Uh, this is Bob.
Say hi, Bob.
"Hi, Bob."
Oh, my gosh, Griffin.
I'm, like, so excited.
This is, like, the nicest
hotel I've ever been to.
Yeah!
Man, this is amazing!
There's so much to do!
Olympic-size swimming pool...
All-you-can-eat buffet...
Full-service spa...
Whoo! I'm gonna get me
a seaweed rewrap!
Wow, it sounds like
everything we can do
at our hotel!
Except on the water!
Ooh! Ah!
Wow!
You nailed it, honey.
Your dad is going to
love this!
Best summer vacation ever!
Wait till you see
the itinerary.
Oh!
That's nice.
Frank, "fire bad." Remember?
Oh, yeah, right, but,
uh, maybe you'll find
your own fireworks
on the cruise, huh?
It's not the Love Boat, Frank.
I'm just here to have fun
with my family.
Huh?
Ha!
Ahoy there!
Welcome aboard!
Whoa! Who is that?
I am Captain Ericka.
And, yes, I'm human. But
don't hold that against me.
I could not be more excited
to have all of you on board
our first-ever
monster cruise!
Whoo-hoo!
Dad? Are you okay?
Eeny feeny fanny
foonyah wah wah?
Oh, no! He's having
a heart attack!
Drac? Not likely.
Yeah, the only heart attack that can
hurt him is with a wooden stake.
It must be a stroke!
Actually, I think
it might be her.
Ow! Watch where you're pointing,
mister, I'm right here.
You always stand
so close to me.
It's creepy.
For so long, monsters were
hiding, living in the shadows,
but not anymore!
You've stood up and waved
your hand or claw or tentacle
and said, "We're here, we're hairy,
and it is our right to be scary!"
Now it's time to celebrate!
You'll enjoy gourmet dining,
thrilling adventures,
and nonstop entertainment,
all on the way
to our final destination,
the lost city
that isn't lost anymore,
Atlantis!
Oh, yeah!
Whoo-hoo!
Whoa!
The fish are acrobats!
They're fishcrobats!
Hello. How y'all doing?
So...
You must be
the one and only Dracula.
I have waited so long
to meet you.
Wow, you really don't age,
do you?
I would kill
for your skin.
Eh doobeeday
shoolah eh koobeeday?
Oh. You're speaking
Transylvanian.
Oh. Always wanted
to learn.
Uh, eh doobeeday
shoolah koobeeday?
- Eh koobeeday.
- Koobeeday.
Eh doobeeday
shoolah koobeeday.
Doolah-day shoolah koobeeday.
Oh, such a romantic language.
You know, there's just
something about an accent
that makes a man
sound so intelligent.
Alibooboo.
That's Transylvanian
right there.
He's saying
it's nice to meet you.
Well, then
"alibooboo" to you as well.
- Alibooboo. Alibooboo.
- Drac! Drac, snap out of it.
Wait. I've always wanted
to do this.
Wake up! Wake up, Drac!
Snap out of it!
Hey, cut it out!
Hey, buddy, you okay?
No, not okay.
Not okay!
I... I...
I...
Zinged.
Mmm!
- Ooh!
- Oh!
Check that out!
Ah!
Here we go.
Mmm, yummy.
Ah!
Papa.
"Kids Club."
What's a kids club?
Whee!
- Fish.
- That's right, dear.
I'm still not sure
I understand.
You take my kids,
all day, on purpose?
Fish.
That's right.
What exactly
don't you understand?
- Why? Ow!
- Shh.
So they can have a great time,
and you can have a great time.
Fish.
Oh, don't worry, you get them
back at the end of the day.
Fish.
Oh, well. That's better
than nothing.
Oh. Oh!
So...
What do we do now?
I think we do
whatever we want.
"Whatever we want"?
Whatever we want.
Whatever we want!
- Stop! Help me!
- Whatever we want.
Oh, hi. Hello.
How y'all doin'?
- Oh.
- Good evening, Captain.
Well, hello.
Oh, my goodness.
Ah!
Would you mind, uh, lifting your tail?
You know...
Oh! Certainly.
Okay. Thank you
so much.
Oh, hello.
Welcome aboard.
Ugh! You were so right,
Great-Grandfather.
Monsters are disgusting!
They're animals!
I'll be right there.
Dracula, is he on board?
Yes. I saw him.
Face-to-face. Ugh!
I was so nice to him.
That pale face of his
and his goofy smile,
showing off his fangs.
Argh, it's just like
you taught me!
It's even worse than I feared!
It was that fateful night
that I realized
a human could never defeat
a monster.
But I wouldn't let
our family legacy die.
And so, I began to search
for an answer.
And I saw it in an ancient text,
an instrument of destruction
so powerful
it destroyed Atlantis,
a whole city of monsters.
And there, deep within the
rubble, it lay, waiting.
Endlessly, I searched
for the lost city
Time passed, and my body
began to fail me.
Oh, it was so sad, Ericka.
First my liver,
then my spleen,
followed by a kidney or two.
Then my golden locks.
But I wouldn't let
that stop me.
I replaced my failing organs
with technology!
Ha-ha!
And look at me now.
Mmm-hmm!
Oh, girl,
it's an improvement, really.
Um, sure.
And now, after 120 years,
I have finally found Atlantis.
Oh, forget about all this!
Let me get rid of
Dracula right now.
I was so close to him,
I could've just...
No, no, no!
We have to
stick to the plan.
Lure the monsters
to Atlantis,
retrieve the instrument
of destruction,
trap them there,
and then wipe them out.
It's simple, Ericka!
Now, promise me you won't
try and kill Dracula.
Ugh, fine!
- I promise.
- Promise what?
I promise I won't
try and kill Dracula. Okay?
Ugh.
Don't worry, Great-Grandfather,
I won't try and kill him...
I will kill him.
Whew!
Ugh!
Oh!
Work it, Dracula.
You know it.
Oh! Lookin' good, Drac!
Feeling good, Frank.
Look at you, so fancy!
What? This? Please.
Ooh! Dressed to impress, huh?
"Impress"? Oh.
Who do I need to impress?
Hey, isn't that
Captain Ericka?
Oh, no!
Uh, what? Eh, oh...
Oops, no,
not her.
Ooh, that's good!
Very amusing.
Sorry, Drac. You know, it's just
we've never seen you like this.
I know.
It doesn't make any sense.
You can't Zing twice,
it's impossible!
But I did! So now what?
And what about Mavis?
She wants you
to be happy, right?
I'm sure she'll go
with the flow.
Oh, no, no, no!
Mavis needs me.
She depends on me.
I need to be home
with my family.
Hey, Murray here may be from
Egypt, but you're the one in
"da Nile."
You guys get that?
Ow! You hit me right in the...
Mavis!
Don't say a word, or
I'll haunt your dreams.
Having fun?
Oh, I'm having even more fun
now that you're here.
You know, Dad, I feel really lucky
to have this time with you.
All of us together,
it's really special.
Me, too,
spider monkey.
Now, are you ready for me to
destroy you in monster ball?
Whoo-hoo! Monster ball!
Come on, Papa Drac!
Bring it on!
For I am king of family fun!
Ha-ha! All right!
Who is ready to get pummeled?
I got to warn you,
I played second-team coed intramural
volleyball at Santa Cruz.
Sure, pal. Whatever you say.
Everybody, just please
watch the hair.
Watch the hair!
Oh-ho-ho! Let's go!
Let's do this!
Oh, my gosh, this is
gonna be so much fun.
Ha-ha! Get ready.
Here comes the pain!
- Spike!
- Not the hair!
Whoa!
No, no, no!
All right!
Captain
Ericka, you are needed on deck.
Next stop...
Buh-bye, Dracula.
Ha-ha! All right, baby!
Oh, baby, I got this.
Hey there, monsters.
Huh?
Yeah! What'd I say!
We're arriving
at our first destination.
The underwater volcano!
Everyone, grab your scuba
gear and get ready to explore
the wonders of the sea.
Especially you,
Count Dracula.
You see that, pal?
She likes you.
Oh, no, no, no.
That sounds like a Zing
in full effect.
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
I'm just here
to have family fun.
Family, family, fun, fun.
Hmm, let's see.
What about here?
Right this way, everyone.
Welcome to one of the true wonders
of the underwater kingdom.
I give you Volcano del Fuego.
Or, as the local sea life
call it...
Whee!
Aw, what a cute family.
What? No, it's not.
Argh! Dracula bad!
Frank, we just ate.
I can't believe
you're hungry already.
I'm sorry.
You know what it is?
It's all... Just all that
seafood just swimming around,
and when I "see food..."
Oh, man! I'm gone.
Oh! Dracula, Dracula, Dracula!
Dracula, Dracula!
I get so close, but it's
almost like he's teasing me.
I just, I can't
stand it anymore.
I have to get him!
Boy, that underwater volcano
looked hot.
Mmm-hmm.
Oh... Hi, Bob.
Right. We promised you we'd
play, uh, ping-pong now.
Um, Dennis?
Who is this?
Uh, it's our friend, Bob.
- Say hi, Bob.
- "Hi, Bob."
Okay! Time to go
play ping-pong.
- Drac!
Hey, boys,
where's the fire?
Oh, well,
Griffin here, he...
- He has something to tell you.
- Me? Uh...
Oh. Yeah, I got this bite on
my hand, and since, you know,
you're a biting expert, I
thought you could take a look.
- Yeah. Come on over here.
- The light is better.
Okay...
Okay, what is going on?
You guys are acting weirder than normal,
and your normal is pretty weird.
You are not gonna believe
what we heard, but...
Shh. I told you I don't
want to upset Mavis.
But what are you talking about?
Okay, well, see, Frank got
hungry, so no surprise there...
But we swam back to the ship, and
we found Ericka raving about you.
She can't live
without you, buddy.
It's serious!
So, Drac, this is great. Are you gonna
make a move on the captain, or what?
Uh, yes.
- Maybe? No.
- Ugh.
It's been a while. I don't
even know where to start.
It's easy, Drac.
Just make some small talk.
- Remember to smile.
- Look into her eyes.
- Keep it casual.
- Say something funny.
Ask her where
her parts are from.
Oh, and say
that her wrappings look nice.
- "Do you like coffins?"
- Compliment her.
- "Your neck looks delicious."
- Here she comes.
Okay, Drac,
hit it.
Your delicious neck wrappings
are in a nice coffin.
Would you like
to see my parts?
Yes, I'd love to go out
with you.
Ay! What?
What?
Cantina. Midnight.
Don't be late.
Whew!
That was a close one.
- Wait! Stop it, Tinkles, stop!
- Wait, Tinkles. Come back.
- Tinkles, stop!
- Wait!
No, no, no!
Tinkles, stop!
I've been found!
You'll never get me, monster!
Shh! Tinkles, stop.
Shh! Shh!
Ew.
Everybody, we are pulling up
to our next stop, the Deserted Island.
It's time to get lost
on the beach,
and we hope you'll find yourself
some fun and relaxation.
Whoo-hoo!
Beach time!
Johnny, you go
set everything up.
And, Dad, you go get in
line for the snow cones.
You know, actually,
I was thinking you and Johnny
should spend
some time together.
What do you call it again?
Eh, date night?
Date night?
- What are you gonna do?
- Well, I thought
me and the guys would
take this opportunity
to spend some quality time
with Dennis.
Oh. Okay.
That's a great idea.
Come on, Johnny.
Date night.
Duh-duh-duh-duh-date night!
Okay, here you go!
- Good girl!
- I got this one.
What was that?
It sounds like our children.
- It is our children! Run!
- Run!
Please! Help! Someone!
Get the parents!
Frank? Would you rub
some moonscreen on my back
before I get burned?
Wait one second, honey.
You know, the kids buried me
in the sand.
Mmm. Thanks, honey.
- Shall we have another?
- Sure.
- Sounds good.
- Straight up.
Isn't this place amazing?
Whoa! The menu is in a bottle!
Genius! Isn't that
awesome, honey?
What? Oh, sorry.
I was just thinking
about my dad.
Don't you think
he's acting weird lately?
Not really. Besides having
a huge crush on the captain.
- What?
- Oh, yeah.
The Love Boat is definitely
making another run.
No way. He's...
He's my dad.
I know, right? It's weird.
When my parents kiss,
I still close my eyes.
I guess I never thought about
him with anyone besides my mom.
You're cool with it,
though, right?
Of course. I want him
to be happy.
Totally.
Buenas noches, mi amigo.
Have you a beverage
to quench me of my parchment?
Yes, of course,
Mr. Chupacabra.
Muchas gracias.
You look ravishing.
Oh.
Uh, thank you. I just...
So, um...
Does Captain Ericka
have a last name?
Uh, oh, uh...
Oh, guacamole!
"Ericka Guacamole"?
That's so international.
No.
Guacamole for us to share.
Oh, how beautiful
is that full moon tonight?
Look. Right behind you.
Mmm! The food here
is to die for.
Holy moly, that was
a lot of guacamole.
Are you feeling all right?
- Totally fine. Why?
- No reason.
Oh...
There must have been garlic
in the guacamole.
Oh, no.
Isn't that deadly
for you?
No, no, no.
It's just that I'm...
Garlic intolerant.
Was that you?
Whoo!
Oh, yeah!
Dolphin surfing!
Whoa!
Hi, Mama. Hi, Papa.
Hey-hey.
Oh! Hey there.
- Papa.
- Hidey-ho!
Hi.
Is my dad
in there, too?
Don't worry,
I'm over here. Bleh, bleh-bleh.
No, Papa Drac's not here.
He's on his date.
Date?
Please, forgive me,
I'm just very nervous.
You see,
I haven't had a date
since my wife died.
How old was your daughter?
She was just an infant.
It was hard
being a single dad,
but I did my best.
I never knew
my mother, either.
Or my father.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Who raised you?
My great-grandfather.
I basically grew up
on this ship.
That's why
you're a captain.
Yeah. It's all
I've ever known.
It was just expected.
You know, a family thing.
I understand,
family is everything.
You have to honor the past.
But we make our own future.
- Dad?
- Mavis!
- Mmm.
- Johnny!
Captain Ericka and I were just
discussing the hospitality industry.
You know,
just work stuff.
You're working now?
This is supposed to be
a vacation.
A family vacation.
I should really go
do captain-y things.
Dad, you said you were
gonna spend time with Dennis.
Dennis. Dennis? Dennis.
Oh! Yeah, you're right.
Where is that kid?
Denisovich? You're
supposed to be with me.
Come on now, kid,
it's family time.
Quit hiding. Dennis?
What was that about?
You mean
your dad's date?
It wasn't a date.
It was work stuff.
Uh-huh.
I'm telling you, Johnny,
there is something about
that woman I don't trust.
But you want your dad
to be happy, right?
Yes.
Just not with her.
Mmm.
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Heads up, honey.
This guac is loaded
with garlic.
Garlic?
Aw! That was
a cute toot, honey.
- We've been up all night!
- Let's stay up all day, too!
Let's get wild!
- Ericka!
- What?
Just where have you been, young lady?
Uh, doing work.
Wearing that?
You were with him!
I know it!
Who?
"Who?" You know who!
You've been sneaking around
my back
trying to kill Dracula again,
haven't you?
So what if I have?
I am a grown woman!
I have the right to kill
whoever I want.
It's not just about you.
You could have ruined
the legacy.
What if he discovered
who you were?
I know. I wasn't thinking.
There's just something about him
that just drives me crazy!
I just, I see him,
and I want to...
Punch him?
Uh... I guess.
Just, I can't wait
to get this over with.
Don't worry,
it won't be long now.
Once you recover the
instrument of destruction,
no one can stop us.
Not even Dracula!
- Oh. Excuse me.
- Spies!
Now, quickly,
before someone comes!
Everyone assemble
on the forward deck.
We are arriving
at our final destination.
From the depths of creation,
the mighty city has risen
once again.
Home to the greatest
monster civilization
the world has ever known,
far surpassing Athens and Rome in
art, culture and sophistication.
I give you the legendary
lost city of Atlantis.
It's a giant Kraken!
Welcome to Atlantis!
Oh!
Ooh. I am so excited!
Come to Daddy!
- Oh.
- Twenty-eight black!
Oh!
- Ahhh!
- Oh, no, you don't.
Last time you gambled, you lost
an arm and a leg. Literally!
- Replacement limbs...
- I'll raise you 40.
...aren't just lying around
like they were in the old days.
So, no gambling.
Frank!
Yes, dear! Got it!
No gambling!
- Tinkles, stop.
- Wait.
- Stop it, Tinkles, stop.
- Ah! Wait!
Have you guys seen Mavis?
I have to find her.
Why? What's going on?
I'm going to tell her
about Ericka.
I can't lie to
my own daughter anymore.
She's the most important
person in the world to me.
I have to tell her the truth.
Right after I talk to Ericka.
Hey.
All right, I'm all...
Frank, are you sure
you know what you're doing?
I got this. I'm all in.
Johnny, have you seen
my dad?
- Maybe he's with Bob.
- Why would he be with Bob?
Bob's a great guy.
- Oh, there he is.
- Who? Bob?
There he is!
Hi, Bob!
Oh.
There it is.
You saved my life.
Of course.
Why wouldn't I?
I just can't believe you
would do that for a human.
Humans, monsters,
what's the difference?
Yeah, right. Right.
Wait. What are you doing here?
Oh, uh... Well, you know,
vampires can predict the future,
so I knew you would
need my help.
Ha! Never heard that before.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a well-known fact.
What are you doing here?
Oh! Uh...
Well, I'm here to get that.
Yeah, it's a family heirloom.
Yeah, it was lost at sea, and
my great-grandfather is... Was!
Uh, was totally obsessed
with getting it back.
So, anywho, thanks for saving my
life, but I can take it from...
Got to be
a little more careful.
How many times
can you save my life, right?
I don't know. Every time?
Really? Well, then...
Wow!
Ah,
that was incredible.
Oh, uh...
Don't you want to get
your family heirloom thingy?
Oh. Right.
Got it.
Mmm.
Oh, here, let me get
that for you.
Dad!
Mavis!
What are you doing
to my father?
Wait! Whoa. Whoa!
Mavis, stop!
Put her down!
No! She's trying to hurt you.
Why can't you see that?
Because I...
Because I Zinged.
What?
I Zinged with Ericka.
No, that can't be true.
You only Zing once.
That's what I thought, too.
"Zing"? What's a Zing?
Uh, well, it's a thing
for monsters.
It's kind of like
our "love at first sight."
What? No. No, no, no.
- You don't even know me.
- Well, not yet.
- But we're just...
- No, you don't understand.
I can't be with you.
I could never be
with someone like you.
I could never be with
a monster.
Dad, I'm so sorry.
- I...
- It doesn't matter.
You heard what she said.
But a Zing never lies.
Ha! You got it!
Yes.
Now that we have
the instrument of destruction,
our family legacy
will be fulfilled.
But first, we'll draw them in
with a dance party!
I love to dance.
Frank,
could you zip me up?
We're gonna be late.
Where did you get those?
Uh, see,
here's the funny thing.
I lost my hands gambling,
but... It's no big deal!
Look, I got these
from the seafood buffet.
Look at this. Clickety-click,
click, clack, clack, click, click.
I kind of like 'em.
I like 'em.
Mmm! Mmm! Mmm.
Mmm. Mmm.
A-ha!
Ah, I guess the party's
this way.
Whoo!
Whoa!
Wow.
Let's get this party
started right!
- Whoo-hoo!
- All right!
What?
Huh?
I thought they said
the party was this way.
DJ in a clamshell?
I'm so jealous.
I can't believe my dad Zinged with
someone who's trying to kill him.
Yeah, the Zing
makes you do crazy things.
Really, Johnny?
What's most important to understand
is that love is an infinite enigma
that is beyond
our understanding.
You and I were two halves,
a world apart.
But then we followed
the strands of destiny
and were brought together.
And our halves made one whole.
But what if she and he...
You must release all the
negativity and look within.
Your bond is unbreakable.
You're right, honey. Wow.
Thanks.
Whoa, you sounded
pretty smart, Dad.
Oh, that? Yeah, it was
just the philosophy
of Sifu Sing from my favorite
TV show when I was a kid,
Kung Fu Shaolin Monk Master.
Anyways, let's get back
to dancing!
Cool.
Dad? You have to talk
to Ericka.
- What?
- I know.
I know what I said before,
but maybe I overreacted
a teensy bit.
It's just the thought
of losing you.
What? What are you talking
about, losing me?
Well, obviously,
after you get married,
you're gonna live on the ship
and travel around the world...
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Slow down, Mavis.
There are two things
I can promise you.
One, nothing can ever take me
from you and all my family.
Two, I will never live
on a boat.
You're my cute
little tarantula.
How could I ever leave you?
Now, seriously,
go talk to her.
I can't. You heard
what she said,
she could never be
with someone like me.
No, Dad.
You're just a half,
and you have to follow your destiny
to find an infinite whole.
You sound like Johnny.
Point is,
you can't deny a Zing.
Monster, human, unicorn...
It doesn't matter.
So go to her! Now!
Okay. I'm on it.
Hey, man, you're
not allowed up here.
The DJ booth is a sacred space.
No. Tinkles, quiet.
Who is this?
Ha! I know you recognize me,
your greatest rival.
Hmm. Oh, right.
You own that Holiday Inn
down by the airport.
No! It is I,
Abraham Van Helsing.
Van Helsing?
After all these years?
You look awful.
Always with the quick insults.
Well, this will shut you up.
And all monsters.
Eh, huh? That's just Ericka's
family heirloom thingy.
Good one, Ericka.
Ericka?
You fool.
Not only is she
the ship's captain,
but she also happens
to be...
Wait. You tell him.
I'm his great-granddaughter.
I'm Ericka Van Helsing.
I knew there was
something wrong with her.
But...
See, what happened...
Now that we're all caught up,
let's get back to the dying.
Behold, the key to the demise
of all monsters.
Let's see.
Right... Okay.
Listen to the melody
of your destruction.
Ooh, what's this little
doodad do?
Yeah!
Hey, look! It's the Kraken.
Everybody out! Now!
We're trapped! Everybody back!
Yay!
Baby!
Papa!
This has to stop now!
Drac, no!
Ah!
Dad!
Mavis!
Time for the immortal Dracula
to die.
Dad!
No!
Ericka!
Bob! Help!
Huh?
Tinkles?
Dennis.
Oh, no.
Bob is Tinkles?
How did he get here?
But thank goodness he did,
'cause look!
You can't do this!
You're wrong
about monsters!
Dracula... He saved my life.
What?
I'm so sorry, Drac.
I was trying to kill you
this whole time,
but then I realized
how wrong I was.
How wrong all of this is.
And then I...
I Zinged.
"Zing"? What's a Zing?
It's a monster thing.
You wouldn't understand.
It's like true love.
Love?
Well, I guess the legacy
ends with me.
Hmm, that's an awkward ending.
Nope!
It's time to start
a new legacy.
A monster-human legacy.
No!
Drac! Van Helsing's beats are
controlling the giant octopus thingy.
If there's one thing I hate,
it's an evil DJ.
We need positive energy!
Get ready for a DJ battle!
You just carry all that
stuff around with you?
Once a bar mitzvah DJ,
always a bar mitzvah DJ.
We're gonna use good music
to defeat his evil music.
- What?
- Trust me, I know the tunes,
but you've got the power.
All right. Okay.
Opening song needs to
be off the shizak.
Ooh, got it. Play this!
What is that noise?
Wow! I like this one.
This feels good.
The fool.
Whoa! His music
is too powerful!
We're gonna need something
even more positive.
Now, Drac!
- Really?
- It has a nice message.
I've had enough
of this nonsense!
Johnny, we need
the most brain-dominating,
toe-tappinating song in the
history of all the universe.
Come on.
Where is it?
I don't know!
There's too many choices.
No, wait!
This is it.
What the...
Boy, that stinks.
It's working!
Hey, Johnny's corny music
is defeating the evil music.
I kind of like it.
Ooh!
No!
Argh! Ahhh! Whoo!
I'm a slave to the rhythm!
No!
Drac, what are you doing?
You got to be greater
than the haters!
Huh?
Why?
Why, after everything,
would you save my life?
Because basically
we are all the same.
Claws or hands, two eyes
or three eyes.
- Green skin.
- No skin.
- Prickly.
- Brainy.
I'm sorry.
Ew.
You are amazing.
Look at me, Dennis.
Look at me.
Come on,
you can't deny it.
No! I'm too young
to Zing!
Well, I feel
kind of silly now.
Heh. For decades
I have hunted your kind,
persecuted you.
The only thing I can do
to make it up to you is
give you
a 30% refund.
Preposterous!
Oh, all right.
Full refund.
Wayne, Wanda,
what happened to you guys?
Yeah, we, like,
hardly saw you on the cruise.
Yeah, I know.
We got tranquilized and spent most
of the trip locked in a closet.
We're gonna book it
again for the holidays.
Hi. Checking in?
Yes. Thank you.
Great. I have a room all ready for you.
Hey, buddy, would you mind?
Sure thing, pal.
Okay, what's going on,
sneaky pants?
Oh, nothing.
It's just, I wanted to make
sure nobody would bother us.
Oh! Why?
Are you going to suck-a my blood?
Bleh, bleh-bleh.
No.
I was going to ask you
if you would marry me.
Well? What do you say?
Will you marry me?
I... I...
Woobee deeba doobee?
Wha...
I mean, I...
woobee doobeedee?
What did she say?
Uh... I'm not sure.
Yes!
Whee!
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resync by GoldenBeard